 <category name="LAPTOP/PC"
			image="images/laptop.png"
			desc="Most Common Laptop/PC Solutions" >
	<title desc="Computer Slows"
			image="images/slow speed.jpg">
		<image ref="images/slow speed.jpg"/>
			<list>
1. Make sure to delete your temporary files:
	a. Search run and click on it or press "windows+R".
	b. Type "%temp%" and delete all files. 
	c. Type "temp" , press continue and delete all files.
	d. Type "prefetch" on run and delete all files.

2. Prevent unused programs from running automatically at the system startup:
    a. Configure startup program from the advanced Task Manager. 
    b. Right click menu on the taskbar- choose task manager.
    c. Click on startup.
    d. Disable all high memory and unnecessary  apps at the startup Eg:- skype, IDM, torrent.

3. Ensure that your computer is not overheating:
    The processor or graphics card clock speed will be throttled back to prevent damage caused by overheating, So
    a.Components should be cooled with large heat sinks and working fans.
    b.Installing a case fan can also help.

4. Click on power option and choose high performance.

5. Your computer's interior should be kept free of dust.

6. Open your Anti-Virus software, ensure that it is upto-date, and run a full scan of your computer to get 	  rid of any possible malware infection which may be slowing your computer down

7. Optimize your hard-disk performance by running disk defragmentor and disk clean-up:
	a. Right clicking on your hard disk in "My computer".
	b. Clicking "Properties". 
	c. Click on "Clean UP".

8. Press "windows+R" and type msconfig:
	a. Jump to services.
	b. Click on "Hide all microsofts" and press ok button.

9.	Press "windows+R" and type "regedit":
	a. Go to "HKEY_CURRENT_USER" select control panel then mouse .
 	b. Set "Mouse Hover Time " to 10.
 	c. Double click on desktop folder and click on "MenuShowDelay".
	d. Set the value into 10.

10. Search "system " in search box and click on advanced system setting:
	a. Click on setting.
	b. click on "Adjust for best performance".
	c. Tick on "Show shadows under mouse pointer".
	d. click on "apply" and "ok".

11. Extent the RAM or replace old CPU.

12. Kill background apps that is not necessary to speed up your pc and net.
</list>
	</title>
	<title desc="Laptop won't turn on "
			image="images/power.jpg">
		<image ref="images/power.jpg"/>
			<list> 

1. If it is a laptop:
    a. Disconnect the power adapter from the laptop.
	b. Remove battery.
	c. Wait 60 seconds.
	d. Reinsert the battery. 
	e. Reconnect the power the power adapter.
	f. Try to turn the laptop on.

2. Check to make sure that the power cable is plugged.

3. Try using another power cable.

4. Check and make sure that the power button isn't stuck.

5. Try to turn on.

 	</list>
	</title>
	<title desc="Monitor/PC won't turn on or Shown No Pictures"
		image="images/disorder.jpg">
		 <image ref="images/disorder.jpg"/>
		<list>

1. Check the power indicator light/ make sure monitor is plugged in.

2. If power indicator light on but you still have no picture,check and make sure that the video cable is 	connected to the CPU firmly.

3. If the monitor power indicator light is green, but you still you can't see a picture, turn the computer 	  off by pressing and holding the power buttom until it turns off.

4. Once it's turned off turn it right back on by pressing power button on the CPU.

5. If you suddenly see a picture you may be having issue with the display settings in windows.

6. Resolution may be set too high - check.

7. Monitor refresh rate may be set improperly- check.

8. Start the system in safe mode.

9. Make any needed display setting changes.

10.Start with the lowest resolution and refresh rate when you make the setting changes.

11.If don't see picture after restart and power indicator on the monitor is green, either hold a lamp or flashlight right in front of the monitor.

12.If you can see the picture in the background with the light on it then the monitor's black-lighting may be malfunctioning and the screen will needed to be replaced.

 </list>
	</title>
	<title desc="Keyboard or Mouse quit working"
		image="images/keyboard.jpg">
		<image ref="images/keyboard.jpg"/>
		<list>

1. If the device have USB connections disconnect the keyboard or mouse and then reconnect them into different USB ports then they were connected before.

2. If keyboard or mouse has ps/2 connection, unplug them and then plug them right back in.

3. If that doesn't work restart the computer.

4. You may have to press and hold the power button until the computer turns off if you haven't any access to a pointing device or a working keyboard.

	</list>
	</title>
	<title desc="Sound doesn't work "
		image="images/sound.jpg">
		<image ref="images/sound.jpg"/>
		<list>

1. Check and make sure that the speakers are turned on and that they have power.

2. Check and make sure that the speakers are plugged into the correct audio jack.

3. It should be color coded and the  correct audio jack will most likely have green around it.

4. Check and make sure that the volume is turned up and isn't muted within windows.

5. Right click on volume icon in the system tray and click "payback devices".

6. Ensure that the right sound device is selected as the default device.

 </list>
	</title>
	<title desc="Windows Start Button Is Gone "
		image="images/windows key.jpg">
		<image ref="images/windows key.jpg"/>
		<list>

1. Hover your pointer around the area where the task bar was originally.

2. If it is reappears, right click the task bar and un-select "Auto hide task bar".

3. Press the "windows keys" to access the "start menu".

4. If task bar has moved, drag and drop it from its current location back to where you want it to be.

 </list>
	</title>
	<title desc="Desktop Icons Out of Order"
		image="images/disorder.jpg">
		<image ref="images/disorder.jpg"/>
		<list>
1. Right click on any open area on desktop.

2. Select "View".

3. Make any needed changes to the icon settings

 </list>
	</title>
	<title desc="Accidentally Delete a File "
		image="images/delete.jpg">
		<image ref="images/delete.jpg"/>
		<list>

1. Check the "Recycle Bin" for missing file.

2. If file is there, simply restore it.

3. If location of the deleted file is unknown, cut it into desktop or drag and drop file into suitable folder

4. If files are not in recycle bin use tools like Photorec, Recuva, Disk Drill, Glary Undelete, Pandora Recovery etc

 </list>
	</title>
	<title desc="Web Browser Text, Too Large or Small"
		image="images/front size.PNG">
		<image ref="images/front size.PNG"/>
		<list>

1. While pressing "Ctrl" key, use the mouse wheel to either shrink or enlarge the web browser text.

 </list>
	</title>
	<title desc=" I Can't Get Online"
		image="images/online.jpg">
		<image ref="images/online.jpg"/>
		<list>

1. Check that WIFI enabled on your computer/ laptop:
	a. Laptop/Pc often have switch function key for WIFI, click on it. 
	b. Check that the network icon on your computer is connected or if there is a yellow warning signal or 	  it is disabled.
	c. If it is connected, call your network provider or get hold on someone with more knowlegde on IT.

2. If WIFI is disabled:
	a. Check whether the cable is connected properly or if WIFI is not on.
	b. If there is a yellow warning, you must reboot the router.
	c. If this doesn't work, try pressing start button.
	d. Type "cmd" into the search box and click Enter.
	e. Black box pops up where u can type "ipconfig/release" then "ipconfig/reneew".
	f. If the internet is not working now, call your Internet Service Provider(ISP).

 </list>
	</title>
	<title desc="Computer Turns off By Itself"
		image="images/power.jpg">
		<image ref="images/power.jpg"/>
		<list>

1. Check First of all that the cables are properly connected.

2. If the computer is very hot, check if the fan needs cleaning of dust.

3. If it is a laptop, whether your battery has deteriorated over time and may need to be replaced.

 </list>
	</title>
	<title desc="Computer Makes Strange Noises"
		image="images/noise.jpg">
		<image ref="images/noise.jpg"/>
		<list>

1. Clean the filter and fan for dust and make sure that all air inlets are free.

2. If you have a laptop, you can try to uninstall and reinstall your sound drivers.

3. If it is a desktop, it may be that the sound card needs replacement.

 </list>
	</title>
	<title desc="Cannot Print From The Web"
		image="images/print.jpg">
		<image ref="images/print.jpg"/>
		<list>

1. Allow temporary pop-ups.

2. You can find legitimate programs that can break the code in a protected PDF document.

3. NOTE: They are usually only legal to use if you or your workplace have the copyright to the document.

</list>
</title>
</category>






