<category name="COMMON DISEASES" desc="The solutions for common disease" image="images/disease.jpg">
    <title desc="High Blood Pressure" image="images/high blood.jpg">
        <image ref="images/high blood.jpg"/>
        <list>
1. Try to lose your weight -- more the weight more will be the blood pressure.

2. Exercise 30 minutes a day.

3. Having more fruits and vegetables will help you to reduce blood pressure.

4. Reduce sodium in your diet:
    a. Avoid processed food.
    b. Don't add more salt on your meal.
    c. Read the labels of food before taking it.

4. Limit the alcohol you drink.

5. Try this
    250gms with horseradish grater, then pour the 2 liters of water and let it boil
        a. Cool the mixture.
        b. Drink it every day -100ml.
        c. Take one week break.
        d.Repeat again.
        e.Regular checkup.

        </list>
    </title>
    <title desc="low Blood Pressure" image="images/low blood.jpg">
        <image ref="images/low blood.jpg"/>
        <list>
1. Eat a diet higher in salt.

2. Limit alcoholic beverages.

3. Drink more fluids during hot weather.

4. Get your regular exercise.

5. Avoid heavy lifting.

6. Avoid straining while on the toilet.

7. Avoid standing still in place for long periods of time.

9. Avoid hot shower and avoid exposing yourself in summer.

10.You can also use following medicine for low blood pressure
    a. Fludrocortisone
    b. Midodrine

        </list>
    </title>
    <title desc="Fever" image="images/fever.jpg">
        <image ref="images/fever.jpg"/>

        <list>
1. Try to cool the temperature of your body:
    a. Soak the washed cloth in cool water.
    b. Sponge the cloth into areas like armpits, feet, hands, groin.
    c. Change the cloth regularly in every 5 mins and repeat.

2. Garlic
    Take garlic with warm water.

3. Ginger
    a. Make ginger tea.
    b. Add some lemon.
    c. Drink.

4. Egg White
    The white part of egg helps you to reduce the body temperature internally.

5. Things to be remembered:
    a. Drink lots of water and orange juice to prevent dehydration.
    b. Don't use use very cold water or ice on the body.
    c. Take complete bed rest for one or two days.
    d. Consume plenty of green leafy vegetables.
    e. Avoid eating refrigerated foods.
    f. Avoid smoking as well as alcoholic drinks.

        </list>
    </title>
    <title desc=" Diabetes/Sugar " image="images/diabetes.jpg">
    <image ref="images/diabetes.jpg"/>
        <list>
1. Things to be remembered:
    a. Keep monitoring your blood sugar levels.
    b. Get plenty of fiber in your diet.
    c. Expose yourself in sunlight - few minutes daily.
    d. Follow the healthy eating plans.
    e. Regular exercise.
    f. Drink plenty of water throughout the day.
    g. Try deep breathing, meditation, listen to your favorite music, work on your hobbies.

2. Foods for curing diabetes
    a. Bitter Gourd -on empty stomach
    b. Cinnamon
    c. Fenugreek
    d. Mango leaves
    e. Curry leaves
    f. Aloe vera
    g. Guava
    h. Okra

        </list>
    </title>
    <title desc=" Headache " image="images/headache.jpg">
        <image ref="images/headache.jpg"/>
        <list>
1. Close your eyes and rest.

2. Seat in a quite, dark room.

3. Sleep frequently to eliminate the pain.

4. Rubbing your neck and temples - to improve blood flow.

5. Warm up your neck

6. Relax - meditate, breath deeply.

7. Drink the water with Tulsi and eat vegetables, fruits regularly.

8. To minimize stress, avoid noisy environment.

9. Take regular meals, breakfast.

10.Try to visualize a peaceful image.
        </list>
    </title>
</category>		