<category name="DRIVING LESSON" desc="Learn Driving" image="images/steering.jpg">

    <title desc="Introduction to vehicle control" image="images/control.jpg">
        <image ref="images/control.jpg" />
        <list>
a. Seat
=> Adjust your seat backward and forward, up and down.

b. Steering
=> Move your car left/right side by steering.

c. Mirrors
=> Helps to see rear and side.

d. Foot Pedals
=> ABC,(Accelerator, Brake, Clutch).

e. Brake
=> To (stop , reduce the speed, control) the vehicle. Brake pedal is usually larger than
acceleration pedal.

f. Accelerator
=> To race the vehicle by passing the more fuels. Accelerator pedal is smaller than
other pedal.

g. Clutch
=> Used for changing gear and to stop the vehicle in slow speed.

h. Gearbox
=> It is power transmission unit, to increase and decrease the speed and force.

i. Blinkers
=> To flash orange light.

j. Wipers
=> To clean your front and back windshields.

        </list>
    </title>

    <title desc="Tips for start to drive" image="images/start driving.jpg">
        <image ref="images/start driving.jpg" />

        <list>
a. Put on your seat belt
=> Driving without a seatbelt is illegal and it is for safety.

b. Check parking brake
=> Down the lever of hand or parking brake.

c. Turn on the engine
=> Put your keys in the ignition and turn clockwise.

d. Shift the Gear
=> By pressing clutch pedal and change the gear by gear lever.

e. Now drive
=> Accelerate your vehicle by acceleration pedal slowly.

f. Congratulations
=> You are driving a vehicle.

g. Steer your vehicle
=> Give desire direction with the help of steering wheel.

h. Use of brake
=> Stop or slowdown your vehicle by pressing the brake pedal.

i. Use of lights
=> Lights can help you see more clearly and avoid danger, you should use them when it's
dark, raining, foggy.

j. Use of wipers
=> You can use wipers while raining, or to clean the windshields.

k. Use of blinkers
=> You can use blinker while turning, lane change and to give signals

l. Use of mirrors
=> Use mirror while turning, overtaking and lane change.
        </list>
    </title>
    <title desc="Parking tips" image="images/parking.jpg">
        <image ref="images/parking.jpg" />
        <list>
a. Find a good parking spot.

b. Stop your vehicle by pressing foot brake.

c. Shift Gear into neutral or park.

d. Turn off your engine by turn the ignition key anticlockwise.

e. Pull off your hand or parking brake.

f. Turn off all lights.

g. Lock your car for security.

        </list>
    </title>
    <title desc="Warning while driving" image="images/warning lights.jpg">
        <image ref="images/warning lights.jpg" />
        <list>
a. Don't forget to obey the speed limit.

b. Don't fight to overtake.

c. Don't sleep while driving.

d. Never drink and drive.

e. Don't forget to turn the indicator light on while turning.

f. Don't forget to check your vehicle condition.

g. Don't ignore vehicle signal.

h. Always obey traffic rules.

i. Don't use mobile phone.

j. Don't talk with passenger.

k. Never drive during sick.

l. Always take necessary documents like licence, blue book.

m. Obey lane rules.

n. Don't drive long without taking rest.

o. Check fuel level.

        </list>
    </title>
    <title desc="Fuel saving tips" image="images/fuel.jpg">
        <image ref="images/fuel.jpg"/>
        <list>
a. Check your tire pressure at least once a month.
=> Low pressure tire consumes more fuel.
=> High pressure makes your tire wear faster.

b. Replace air filter, fuel filter, oil filter, spark plug, injectors, oxygen sensor regularly as per the manual.

c. Driving in highest gear possible without laboring the engine
=> 60 km/hr use 25% more fuel than in fifth gear than it would be in third gear.

d. Try to drive smoothly, avoid heavy braking
=> Influence the fuel economy by 30%.

e. Old battery cables cause the alternator to work harder consuming more fuel.
=> Clean or replace the corroded battery cables

f. Start the engine, wait for 20 seconds and drive away.

g. Don't let the vehicle idle for more than five minutes.

h. More load consume more fuel therefore lighten the load.

i. Remove roof rack, heavy seats unnecessary load if not needed.

j. Always use manufacture's recommended grade of oil.

k. Don't use contaminated, dust containing, impure and cheap oil and fuel.

l. Thicker oil is harder to pump, so don't use thicker oils in the engin, gearbox.

m. Avoid rough/ off roads whenever possible, off road driving consumes 30 % more fuel than normal roads.

n. Inspect suspension, spring, ball joints, pedals, steering linkage, hub greasing, tire trades regularly.

o. Avoid "revving " the engine especially just before the engine shuts off.

        </list>
    </title>
</category>





