<category name="HEALTH TIPS " desc="Some Useful Health Tips" image="images/health tips.png">
    <title desc="Tips" image="images/health tips.png">
        <image ref="images/health tips.png"/>
        <list>
1. Answer the phone calls with left ear.

2. Do not have heavy meal after 5 pm.

3. Do not drink coffee thrice a day.

4. Drink plenty of water in the morning, less in the evening

5. Light exercise...Tight sleep......Right eat

6. Do not eat pills with cool water

7. Don't eat spicy, oily food

8. Do not go to bed immediately after taking medicines

9. Do not wear high heels

10.Soda is danger of diet

11.Vitamin D daily is recommended

12.Tulsi improves memory power

13.Lemon is solution of indigestion and stomach ache

14.Never ignore your pains

15.Smiling makes you healthy and happy

16.Avoid tight clothes

17.Do not skip breakfast

18.Tomatoes reduce the risk of heart disease

19.Breast feeding increases intelligence

20.Simple exercise enhance your memory skills

21.Garlic helps to boost your sperm count, prevent pimple, improve imunity power

22.Manage your blood pressure for longer life

23.Never keep your mobile under your pillow

24.You should consume more vegetables and fruits to enhance immunity power

25.Saffron, Broccoli, oats,apples,green tea,dark chocolate, improve your brain power

26.Men should eat tomatoes, it reduces level of stress

27.Avoid quick eating

28.Never go to sleep with full stomach

29.Formula for healthy weight :- weight = Height in cm - 100

30.Magnesium is essential in regular diet

31.Bananas help to balance the junk foods, act as against heartburn , make you smarter

32.Onions for strong erection during sex

33.Honey is skin lightning agent, helps in get rid of dry cough

34.Positive thinking makes u young, smart, beautiful/handsome, creative, innovative

35.Use coconut oils to avoid infection

36.10 gm Tulsi mixed with equal amount of ginger juice help in proper digestion of
foods

37.Chocolate is actually good for heart disease cure and makes you active, energetic

38.Mushrooms fights against cancer

39.Do not drink water from plastic bottle, it contain BPA which is harmful to health

40.Too much carbohydrates make you lazy
        </list>
    </title>
</category>	

