<category name="WAY TO SUCCESS"
			image="images/success.jpg"
			desc="Way to inspire">
	<title desc="Inspiration Quotes"
			image="images/success.jpg">
			<image ref="images/success.jpg"/>
				<list>
1. Before you talk, listen. Before you react, think. Before you criticize, wait. Before	you pray, forgive. 	  Before you quit, try. 

2. Accept your past without regret, handle your present with confidence and face your future without fear.

3. Keep calm, you may be weak but god is strong.

4. You can not start the next chapter of your life if you keep re-reading the last one.

5. When you judge me without knowing me you do not define me, you define yourself.

6. The people who truly care wil always find a way back into your life.

7. I do not need the whole world to love me, I just need a few sincere and great people who can accept me.

8. Stars can not shine without darkness.

9. Do not worry about failures, worry about the chance you miss when you don't even try.

10.Never judge a situation that you have never been in.

11.Learn to wait there is always time for everything.

12.No-one is perfect, that is the reason why pencils have erasers.

13.A man with dreams, needs a women with vision.

14.Confidence is the key. If you do not believe in yourself, then nobody will.

15.Everyone you meet has something to teach you.

16.Life does not have to be perfect to be wonderful.

17.You will never live a happy life if you always care about what others think about you.

18.Inspire yourself to learn something new everyday.

19.Do not compare your progress with that of others, we all need our own time to travel our own distance.

20.Trust is like a eraser, it gets smaller with each mistake.

21.If you are not good enough for someone, they are not good enough for you.

22.Cheaters think everyone cheats. Liar think everyone lies. Keep this in your mind.

23.Pain is the best teacher.

24.Be real, be yourself, be unique, be true, be honest, ba humble, be happy.

25.Many girls want attention, real women want respect.

26.Something I learn about people ... if they do it once, they will do it again.

27.Feel your beauty and enjoy your smiles.

28.Sometimes complicate questions have simple solutions.

29.We all have those secrets we would never tell to anyone.

30.Evil and good are God's right and left.

31.Nice people do not necessarily fall in love with nice people.

32.Everybody is a genius. You can not judge a fish by its ability to climb a tree.

33.I Never lose. Either I win or I learn.

34.Never judge someone, everyone has a story.

35.Do not wait for a opportunity, make one.

36.Take exam, know your score, move on.

37.Stop saying "I wish" and start saying "I will".

38.Winning isn't everything but wanting to win is.

39.Putting yourself first isn't selfish, it's necessary.

40.Sometimes losing some people is actually a game.

41.Forgive. But Don't forget.

42.Life is like riding a bicycle. To keep your balance you must keep moving.

43.If you don't like something, change it. If you can't change it, change your 	attitude.

44.Learn to say "NO" sometimes.

45.Accept what you can't change. Change what you can't accept.

46.Silence is best way to let someone know they did you wrong.

47.Work hard in silence, let success make the noise.

48.Two things define you: your patience when you have nothing, and your attitude when you have everything.

49.Don't put the key to your happiness in someone else's pocket.

50.Forgive them even if they are no sorry.

				</list>
				</title>
</category>