<category name="SELF MOTIVATION TIPS"
			image="images/inspire.jpg"
			desc="Boost your inner power">
	<title desc="motivational tips"
			image="images/inspire.jpg">
			<image ref="images/inspire.jpg"/>
			<list>
1. Do not compare yourself with others.

2. Do not confuse the path with the destination.

3. If you lose someone, find yourself.

4. Ideas and words can change the world.

5. Do not be afraid of any rejections, it's part of your life.

6. The best revenge is to improve yourself.

7. Just because you can't sing, doesn't mean you won't sing.

8. It only take one person to change your life, that is YOU.

9. You need new haters to improve yourself.

10.Do not choose the better person, choose the person who makes you better.

11.Do not expect anything from anyone.

12.Never lower your standards to keep someone.

13.Good times become good memories, bad times becomes good lesson.

14.Do not call it problems, instead, call it challenges.

15.Smile.your enemies hate it.

16.Never stop believing in you.

17.Forget about people that brings you down and just live your life.

18.Just do whatever makes you happy.

19.Think, plan, concentrate and start.

20.Life is easy for- who knows how to live.

21.Look around you and enjoy what you see.

22.What hurts you today, makes you stronger tomorrow.

23.Enjoy simple pleasures in life.

24.Do not let yourself be controlled by people, money, past experience.

25.Make it your habit to do what makes you proud.

26.Try to see good in everyone.

27.Happiness is choice. Choose it.

28.Never give up something you really want.

29.Bad things happen everyday to everyone. The difference is in how people deal with it.

30.Not everyone will understand you.

31.Move on from the people who keep ruining your happiness

32.You were born to make mistakes, not fake perfections.

33.Do not tell your plans, show them your result.

34.Do not listen to what people say, watch what they do.

35.Never stop trying.

36.None is in control of your happiness expect YOU.

37.Being positive in negative situation is not naive. Its leadership.

38.Count your blessings, not your problem.

39.You do not need anyone who do not need you.

40.Everyday may not be good but there is something good in everyday.

41.Mistakes are proof that you are trying.

42.There is beauty in simplicity.

43.Over thinking kills yourself.

44.Just live the moments with no expectations.

45.Discover your natural happiness.

46.People only hear what they want to hear.

47.Happiness is highest level of success.

48.Your struggle is part of your story.

49.Always find a reason to smile.

50.There are no secrets to success. It is the result of preparation, hard work and learning from failure.
				</list>
	</title>
</category>
